Harold Seo

haroldseo.github.io/portfolio/ - linkedin.com/in/haroldseo/ - github.com/haroldseo Los Angeles, CA - (213) 327-6225 - harold.seo.612@gmail.com

Summary:

I'm a web developer working in JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, React.js, Node.js and Ruby on Rails. Prior to becoming a web developer, I worked as an accounts receivable specialist at Promesa USA. My responsibilities included tracking orders, confirming transactions/payments, and maintaining records. Currently, I'm working on a React application called ChatApp, a platform for users to communicate through chat.

Technical Skills:

- Languages: JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, Ruby

- Frameworks & Libraries: React.js, Express, Node.js, Rails, jQuery, Bootstrap

Databases: MongoDB, PostgreSQL

 Other Technologies: Git and Github, Heroku, AWS, JSON Web Tokens, AJAX, SASS, WordPress, Passport.js, Socket.io, Google Maps API, Twilio API, API.AI

Projects:

1. ChatApp

A web application, for users to communicate through chat. Users have the option of chatting in a global chatroom, private chatrooms, or to a ChatBot. This application was built using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, React.js, Node.js, Express, MongoDB, Bootstrap, JWT, Socket.io, and API.AI.

2. Dozer

A web application that alerts the user through call or text when they are approaching their destination. This application was built using Node.js, Express, AJAX, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Passport.js, Bootstrap, MongoDB, Twilio API, and Google Maps API.

3. But First, Coffee

A full-stack application for users to find local coffee shops and review them. This application was built using Ruby on Rails, HTML5, CSS3, and Bootstrap.

4. Tag, You're It

A two-player game of tag. This game was built using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, and jQuery.

Experience:

1. Accounts Receivable Specialist

Promesa USA Jan 2017 – Jul 2017

2. Accounts Payable Specialist

BBCN Bank Jun 2015 – Aug 2015

Education:

1. General Assembly

Web Development Immersive, 2017

2. California State University Northridge

Bachelor of Science (BS), Kinesiology and Exercise Science, 2010 - 2016